https://photokunst.com/policies/privacy-policy/

photokunstNavigationSkip to contentHomeArtistsConsultingLicensingExhibitionsCurrent ExhibitionsAbout Our ExhibitionsBooksFeaturedErnest Brooks II: Current Print OffersKenneth Parker: Tibetan MustangLuigi Fieni: Tibetan MustangHEINRICH HARRER: Tibetan PortfolioMarissa Roth: Infinite Light collectionBlog & NewsPhotokunstAbout UsPoliciesSales & Copyright PoliciesPrivacy PolicyContactPrivacy PolicyThis Privacy Statement sets forth the information gathering, use, and dissemination practices of photokunst, LLC (“photokunst”) in connection with the World Wide Web site located at www.photokunst.com (the “Site”). We have always taken your privacy seriously. We do not share your information details with third parties.This Privacy Statement addresses photokunst’s practices regarding information collected only directly through or from the Site – it does not address or govern any information gathering, use, or dissemination practices related to information collected other than directly through or from the Site, including, without limitation, from or via telephone, facsimile, postal mail, personal delivery, or other or additional offline means or media. photokunst can be contacted by mail at 725 Argyle Avenue, Friday Harbor, WA, 98250, by phone at 360-378-1028, or by e-mail at info@photokunst.comCollection of Personal Information from Site Visitorsphotokunst may collect or track (1) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with photokunst via e-mail, and (2) information knowingly provided by the visitor in online forms, registration forms, surveys, e-mail, and other online avenues (including, without limitation, demographic and personal profile data). Personal information, such as user’s name, address and contact information, may be gathered from you on a voluntary basis, at various times on the site. Users need not submit this information to use the site. When visitors perform searches within the Site, photokunst may record information identifying the visitors or linking them to the search performed. Photokunst may also record limited information for every search request and use that information to solve technical problems with the services available directly or indirectly in connection with the Site and to calculate overall usage statistics.Comments and Cookiesphotokunst uses first party cookies (local) for analytics. No third party cookies (links to advertising or marketing networks) are used. When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment. If you leave a comment on our blog pages you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.Use of Personal Data CollectedPersonal data collected by photokunst may be used by photokunst for many reasons, for example, for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users’ behavior, for content improvement, for fulfillment of a requested transaction or record keeping, or to customize the content and layout of the Site. Aggregate data and individually identifying information, such as names, postal, and e-mail addresses, phone numbers, and other personal information which visitors voluntarily provide to photokunst may be added to photokunst’s databases and used for future calls and mailing regarding Site updates, new products and services, and upcoming events.Newsletter and e-message campaignsTo our subscribers, we hope that you enjoy receiving news about photokunst’s photographers, exhibitions, special offers and events. photokunst is committed to protecting your personal information. We use your personal data (name and e-mail address) for the exclusive purpose of sending you our newsletter. We do not share your information details with third parties. As we work with Mailchimp, you can also review Mailchimp’s privacy policy.  Should you wish to unsubscribe  you may do so at any time.
